

Info

- pellabeuf@gmail.com
- Paris, France
- In Linkedin
- Github
- Medium
- X X

Profile

With 5 years of experience in full stack and blockchain development, I am a passionate and determined developer. My goal is to continue learning and excelling in the field of blockchain, in order to actively contribute to this rapidly expanding ecosystem.

Languages

French, English

Interests

Technology and Innovation Blockchain Finance Real Estate Sports

Foulques Pellabeuf

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

Technical Skills

Programming Languages

TypeScript Solidity NestJs Docker React/Next.js Rust Database **AWS** Tailwind Circom ORM Grafana Noir-lang Elasticsearch Angular Sequelize Bootstrap Hardhat/Forge Prisma Redis

Subgraph GraphQL

Experiences

Onbrane

2023 - Present

Lead Blockchain Developer

I develop a decentralized financial application EVM for a financial company that has seen €5 trillion + exchanged, using cryptographic techniques such as ZKP and homomorphic encryption to ensure the privacy of debt products.

Freelance

Blockchain Developer

I developed protocols on **Uniswap V4** and created financial applications reaching **\$500K+** in TVL

Hexalabs

2022 - 2023

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer

I developed frontends with React.js and Next.js, deployed blockchain projects in Solidity (**DeFi, NFT Marketplace**, etc.), and built backends.

Toys films

2020 - 2022

Full Stack Developer

With Angular and various node.js frameworks, I designed innovative solutions for major clients such as **L'Oréal**, **Microsoft**, and **Air Liquide**.

Education

Hetic university

2017 - 2020

Computer science bachelor

Training focused on real-time 3D content creation, covering **applied mathematics** and **web development**.